Summer Love is a tv movie, romance film directed by Lynne Stopkewich.
Maya Sulliway is a struggling single mom who's studying to become an accountant.
When her young daughter goes off to sleepaway camp, Maya accepts a summer internship at Kizzmit, a tech
company known for developing a popular social app, in order to receive college credit.
Maya Sulliway, played by Rachael Leigh Cook.
Colin Fitzgerald, played by Lucas Bryant.
Will Martin, played by Travis Milne.
Josh Moss, played by Aidan Kahn.
Chantal, played by Crystal Balint.
Freshman, played by Matt Visser.
My Summer of Love is a 2004 British drama film directed by Paweł
Pawlikowski and co-written by Pawlikowski and Michael Wynne.
Based on the 2001 novel of the same name by Helen Cross, the film explores the romantic
relationship between two young women from different classes and backgrounds.
Working class Mona (Natalie Press), whose once-hotheaded brother Phil (Paddy Considine) became a born-again Christian in prison, meets
upper middle class Tamsin (Emily Blunt, in her theatrical film debut) who suffers from a lack of love in her family.
Filmed in West Yorkshire, the film went on to win a BAFTA.
The tone is emotional.